Ferguson, Robert H., Papers /4001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert H. Ferguson Papers
1933-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Ferguson, Robert H.
/4001
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Consists mainly of material regarding farmworkers and rural labor.
3082580
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3051: Albert Martin Papers
Ferguson, Robert Harry.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3082580
- Rural Development, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A Preliminary Appraisal of Concerted Services in Training and Education in Rural Areas, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Concerted Services in Training and Education: An Evaluation of Development Change, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Manpower Report of the President, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A Manpower Program for Rural Areas, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Farm Union Research, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Labor Relations Acts, 1941-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A Compendium of Papers -The Ohio State University-, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Economic and Social Considerations in Extending Unemployment Insurance to Agricultural Workers, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Impact of Extension of Unemployment Insurance to Agriculture, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Rural Development, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Research Application in Rural Economic Development and Planning, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Optimal Regional Funding of Elementary and Secondary Schooling, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Concerted Services in Minnesota an Evaluation of Developmental Change, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Concerted Services in Arkansas: An Evaluation of Developmental Change, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- The concerted Services Approach to Developmental Change in Rural Areas: An Interim Evaluation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Misc., 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Arizona Agricultural Employment Relations Board, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- California + Unions and Poverty, 1926-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Labor References (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Boxed
- 223.131 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 223.131 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 223.131 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 223.131 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 223.131 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 223.131 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 223.131 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 223.131 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 223.131 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 223.131 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 223.131 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 223.131 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 223.131 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 223.131 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 223.131 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 223.131 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 223.131 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 223.131 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 223.131 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 223.131 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 223.131 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 223.131 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 223.131 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 223.131 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 223.131 1947-1948 ILR Faculty Meetings (Box 2, Folder 25)
- N.Y.S. Joint Legislative Committee on ILR, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- N.Y.S. Joint Legislative Committee on ILR, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- N.Y.S. Joint Legislative Committee on ILR, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- The Journal of Behavioral Economics, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Center for Rural Manpower and Public Affairs, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- New York - Agriculture Labor Bill 7274-B (1971-72 session), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Farm Population, Employment, Earnings, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Federal Legislative Proposals, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Fisher, Dennis, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Food Processing Agreements, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Food Processing Ind., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Rural Manpower - Local Conferences, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Rural Manpower National Conferences, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Rural Manpower Proposals, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Teamsters, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- United Farm Workers, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- United Farm Workers (Salandini), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- United Farm Workers Press Clippings, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Notes, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Manuscript, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Agricultural Unionism Papers and Talks Ferguson, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Organizations, N.Y.S., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Agricultural Unionism Articles, 1968-1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Donovan-Aronson Agriculture, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Proposal Agricultural Labor Relations Bill, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Idaho, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Kansas, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Arizona, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Massachusetts, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Other States, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Hawaii, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Wisconsin, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)